<?xml version="1.1" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<projects>
  <project>
    <name>Victory Merch</name>
    <image>victorymerch.jpg</image>
    <summary>E-commerce shop built from the grounds up using a custom CMS. Includes credit card processing, user account overview, digital downloads and wishlists.</summary>
    <keywords>git, php, responsive, ecommerce, purecss, grunt</keywords>
  </project>
  <project>
    <name>Victory Records</name>
    <image>victoryrecords.jpg</image>
    <summary>Landing page of a rock label with artists information, releases, tour schedule, music videos and lyrics.
    </summary>
    <keywords>git, php, responsive, bootstrap</keywords>
  </project>
  <project>
    <name>Another Victory</name>
    <image>anothervictory.jpg</image>
    <summary>Publishing company focused on music licensing. Has pre-set and custom playlists, opens/plays/downloads
      tracking and option to stream or download individual tracks and playlists.
    </summary>
    <keywords>git, php, jquery, responsive, bootstrap</keywords>
  </project>
  <project>
    <name>Victory Press Center</name>
    <image>victorypresscenter.jpg</image>
    <summary>One stop hub for all the resources press might need for Victory Records' artists. High res photos, logos,
      tour dates and more available individually or a ZIP download. Includes press releases archive as a Wordpress
      module.
    </summary>
    <keywords>git, php, jquery, responsive, bootstrap</keywords>
  </project>
  <project>
    <name>Overlord</name>
    <image>overlord.jpg</image>
    <summary>Admin control panel used to maintain Victory Records, Merch, Press Center and more. Has merch sizing,
      orders control panel, artists, releases information, tour dates and more.
    </summary>
    <keywords>git, php, gulp, haml, twig, jquery, responsive, bootstrap</keywords>
  </project>
  <project>
    <name>Shirts Now</name>
    <image>shirtsnow.jpg</image>
    <summary>Screen printing shop with products and colors for each garment, product quotes and FedEx shipping
      information based on the ZIP code.
    </summary>
    <keywords>git, php, jquery, responsive, bootstrap</keywords>
  </project>
  <project>
    <name>Eternal Enemies</name>
    <image>eternalenemies.jpg</image>
    <summary>Facebook application that takes your profile picture and superimposes album artwork to create a new image
      with a scarf on your face and sets it as you profile picture.
    </summary>
    <keywords>php, jquery, mobile first, facebook</keywords>
  </project>
  <project>
    <name>Bahamas Hurricane Relief</name>
    <image>bahamashurricanerelief.jpg</image>
    <summary>Quick one afternoon project to make a landing page with donation information for the hurricane Joaquin victims.</summary>
    <keywords>html, jquery, bootstrap, responsive</keywords>
  </project>
  <project>
    <name>Promo pages</name>
    <image>promo.jpg</image>
    <summary>Promo landing pages for ad campaigns, with call to action and specific purpose for 20+ artists.</summary>
  </project>
  <project>
    <name>EPK</name>
    <image>epk.jpg</image>
    <summary>Electronic Press Kits used to pitch songs, music videos and tours to industry contacts. Each page was custom designed taking into consideration the audience and expected result.</summary>
  </project>
  <project>
    <name>Secure Stream</name>
    <image>secure.jpg</image>
    <summary>Streaming site for unreleased songs and albums. Each track has voiceover for tracking leaked music, usage is monitored and plays are non downloadable (RTMP stream).</summary>
  </project>
  <project>
    <name>Victory Street Team</name>
    <image>victorystreetteam.jpg</image>
    <summary>Signup page for Victory Street Team, a collection of fans who promote artists, releases and shows in exchange for albums, merchandise and tickets.</summary>
  </project>
</projects>